Finding Aid for Center for Research on Learning and Teaching (University of Michigan) records, 1961-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Grants 1965-2000, 13 linear feet
  - Faculty Development Fund
    - 1980
      - Proposals (Box 7)
      - Dean's letters (Box 7)
      - Adams, Gerald (Box 7)
      - Aller, Hugh; Astronomy (Box 7)
      - Althoen, Steven, Mathematics (Box 7)
      - Anderson, William; Engineering (Box 7)
      - Beauchamp, Charles; Medical (Box 7)
      - Boggs, Kathleen; Nursing (Box 7)
      - Borer, Katarina and Timothy White; Physical Education (Box 7)
      - Chudacoff, Edward; Music (Box 7)
      - Griffin, H.; Chemistry (Box 7)
      - Davidson, Terrence; Education, 2 folders (Box 7)
      - Donahue, Craig; Chemistry (Box 7)
      - Elliot, Robert; Engineering (Box 7)
      - Gamson, William; Sociology (Box 7)
      - Gates, David; Biology (Box 7)
      - Goldberg, J; Mathematics (Box 7)
      - Hildebrandt, Herbert; Business Administration (Box 7)
      - Joindes, John; Psychology (Box 7)
      - Katha, C.P.; Management (Box 7)
      - Kim, Jaegwon; Philosophy (Box 7)
      - Kuhns, L.R.; Medical (Box 7)
      - Larson, Myra; Art (Box 7)
      - Lorey, Robert; Dentistry (Box 7)
      - McClatchey, Kenneth; Dentistry (Box 7)
      - Marsh, Ronald; Mathematics (Box 7)
      - Olson, Charles; Natural Resources (Box 7)
      - Scholl, Geraldine; Education (Box 7)
      - Segal, Howard; Engineering (Box 7)
      - Thompson, Clairborne; Germanic Languages and Literature (Box 7)
      - Williams, William; Engineering (Box 7)
      - Wolfe, David; Spanish (Box 7)
      - General (Box 7)
    - 1981
      - General, 2 folders (Box 8)
      - Blackford, George; Economics (Box 8)
      - Brown, Kathleen; Geography (Box 8)
      - Coyle, Peter and Roy Glover; Anatomy (Box 8)
      - Crane, S.; Public Health (Box 8)
      - Goff, Gerald; Social Work (Box 8)
      - Gordon, Jesse; Social Work (Box 8)
      - Griffin, Henry; Chemistry (Box 8)
      - Humesky, Assya; Slavic Literature and Languages (Box 8)
      - Katopedes, Nikolaos; Civil Engineering (Box 8)
      - Lawler, John; Linguistics (Box 8)
      - Miller, Kenton; Natural Resources (Box 8)
      - Mutschler, Elizabeth; Social Work (Box 8)
      - Razzoog, Micheal; Dentistry (Box 8)
      - Rosenberg, Victor; Library Science (Box 8)
      - Shannon, Micheal; Pharmacy (Box 8)
      - Stout, Louis; Music (Box 8)
      - Whitehouse, Frank and Harry Douthit; Medical School (Box 8)
      - Zitzewitz, Paul; Natural Science (Box 8)
    - 1982
      - Survey of Non-Recipients (Box 8)
      - General (Box 8)
      - Boustany, Nader; Electrical Engineering (Box 8)
      - Burdi, Alphonse; Medical School (Box 8)
      - Crowley, Dennis; Medical School (Box 8)
      - Gelderloos, Orin; Natural Sciences (Box 8)
      - Humesky, Assya; Slavic (Box 8)
      - Kotowicz, William; Dentistry (Box 8)
      - Schultz, Jerome; Chemical Engineering (Box 8)
      - Stevenson, Dwight; Engineering (Box 8)
      - Vakalo, Emmanual-George; Art-Architecture (Box 8)
      - Wendel, James; Mathematics (Box 8)
    - 1983
      - Brandle, Kurt; Art and Architecture (Box 8)
      - Brilliant, Lawrence; Public Health (Box 8)
      - Cooper, Frederick; Residential College (Box 8)
      - Donabedian, Dorothy; Nursing (Box 8)
      - Dvorak, Tricia; Romance Language (Box 8)
      - Folger, H.S.; Engineering (Box 8)
      - Kaufman, Phillip; Biology (Box 8)
      - Kleinsmith, L.; Biology (Box 8)
      - Lohmann, Jack; Engineering (Box 8)
      - Neuhoff, David; Computer Engineering (Box 8)
      - Nowack, Paul; Natural Resources (Box 8)
      - Toon, Thomas; English and Philosophy (Box 8)
      - Woo, Tony; Engineering (Box 8)
    - 1984
      - Bement, Spencer; Electrical Engineering and Computer Science (Box 8)
      - Chin, Bruce; Public Health (Box 8)
      - Coffin, Edna; Near Eastern Studies (Box 8)
      - Danielson, Lee; Business (Box 8)
      - Feldstein, Paul; Public Health (Box 8)
      - Hales, David; Natural Resources (Box 8)
      - Lachance, Micheal; Mathematics and Statistics (Box 9)
      - Mann, Richard; Psychology, 2 folders (Box 9)
      - Moore, Frederick; Dentistry (Box 9)
      - Snyder, James; Architecture and Urban Planning (Box 9)
      - Wehrer, Joseph and Emanuel-George Vakalo, Architecture (Box 9)
      - Wixson, Karen; Education (Box 9)
      - General (Box 9)
    - 1985
      - Ard, Joseph and John Swales; English Language Institute (Box 9)
      - Coffin, Edna; Near Eastern Studies (Box 9)
      - Gregory, David; Music (Box 9)
      - Folger, H.S.; Engineering (Box 9)
      - Goodman, Frederic; Education (Box 9)
      - Hessler, David; Library Science (Box 9)
      - Jenkins, Janice; Engineering (Box 9)
      - Kozma, Robert; Education (Box 9)
      - Lewis, Robert; Physics (Box 9)
      - Marzolf, Marion; Communication (Box 9)
      - Ness, Gayl; Sociology (Box 9)
      - Nyden, Marc; Chemistry (Box 9)
      - Starks, David; Dentistry (Box 9)
      - Sue, David; Behavioral Science (Box 9)
      - White, Timothy; Physical Education (Box 9)
      - Wolfe, Robert; Public Health (Box 9)
      - General (Box 9)
    - 1986
      - Berger, Carl; School of Education (Box 9)
      - Borders, James; Music History (Box 9)
      - Brown, Terry; Landscape Architecture (Box 9)
      - Flynn, Marilyn and Sydney Bernard, Social Work (Box 9)
      - Hansen, Kristina; Math (Box 9)
      - Ikuma, Hiroshi; Biological Science (Box 9)
      - Ingram, William; English (Box 9)
      - Kerschbaum, W.E.; Dentistry (Box 9)
      - Maxim, Bruce; Mathematics (Box 9)
      - O'Conner, Pat; Dentistry (Box 9)
      - Robinson, Terry; Psychology (Box 9)
      - van der Pluijm, Ben; Geological Science (Box 9)
      - Volakis, John; Engineering (Box 9)
      - Warner, Robert; Library Science (Box 9)
    - 1986/87
      - 1986
        - Boonyatinkarn, S/N; Architecture & Urban Planning (Box 16)
        - Collett, L.S.; Education (Box 16)
        - Hazlett, B.; LS&A (Box 16)
        - Jones, Carol; Natural Resources & Environment (Box 16)
        - Keyes, R.; LS&A (Box 16)
        - Maxim, Bruce; Computer Science (Box 16)
        - Olson, Lorraine; Engineering (Box 16)
        - Paris, S.; Education (Box 16)
        - Volakis, J.L.; Engineering (Box 16)
        - Wolliscroft, J; Medicine (Box 16)
        - General (Box 16)
      - 1987-Spring
        - Bernal, L.P.; Aeronautical Engineering (Box 16)
        - Burkel, W.; Medical School (Box 16)
        - Dandekar, H.; Architecture & Urban Planning (Box 16)
        - Daniel, L; Nursing (Box 16)
        - Goldberg, D. (Box 16)
        - Knight & Walcott; Dentistry (Box 16)
        - Kooman, J; Epidemiology (Box 16)
        - Ludema, K; Electrical Engineering and Computer Science (EECS) (Box 16)
        - Marzolf, M.; Communication (Box 16)
        - Nairn, R.; Immunology (Box 16)
        - Patterson, R.; Natural Resources (Box 16)
        - Sharp, R.; Chemistry (Box 16)
        - Williams, Reg A.; Psychiatric Nursing (Box 16)
        - Yaffee, S.L.; Natural Resources (Box 16)
        - General (Box 16)
    - 1987/88
      - 1987-Fall
        - Barclay, M.; OB-Gyn (Box 16)
        - Beudert, P; Music School (Box 16)
        - Brandle, K; Architecture & Urban Planning (Box 16)
        - Buss, D., Psychology (Box 16)
        - Knudsvig, G.; Classical Studies (Box 17)
        - Rammuny, R. Near East Studies (Box 17)
        - Springer, N.; Nursing (Box 17)
        - Williams, W.; Engineering (Box 17)
      - 1988-Winter
        - Carver, P.; Pharmacy (Box 17)
        - Eley & Somers; Sociology/History (Box 17)
        - Pek, S.; Internal Medicine (Box 17)
        - Peterson, C.; Psychology (Box 17)
        - Plochinski, K.; Program Initiatives (Box 17)
        - Rosenberg, W.; History (Box 17)
        - Savage, P.; Chemical Engineering (Box 17)
        - Sowers, M.; Epidemiology (Box 17)
        - Van Dam, R.; History (Box 17)
    - 1988/89
      - 1988-Fall
        - Casa, Frank; Romance Languages (Box 17)
        - Connelly, Thomas; Anatomy & Cell Biology (Box 17)
        - Gregory, Wm.; Dentistry (Box 17)
        - Ingram, William; English (Box 17)
        - Katopodes, Nikolaos; Civil Engineering (Box 17)
        - Seabury, Brett; Social Work (Box 17)
        - Tosney, Kathryn; Biology (Box 17)
        - General (Box 17)
      - 1989-Winter
        - Blumenfield, Phyllis (Box 17)
        - Dahm, Werner; Aeronautical Engineering (Box 17)
        - Ege, Seyhan; Chemistry (Box 17)
        - Gregory, David; Music (Box 17)
        - Kmenta, Jan; Economics (Box 17)
        - Patt, Yale; Electrical Engineering and Computer Science (EECS) (Box 17)
        - Stewart, Abigail; Psychology (Box 17)
        - General (Box 17)
    - 1989/90
      - 1989-Fall
        - Birmingham, Wm.; Digital Systems (Box 17)
        - Carnahan/Wilkes; Chemical Engineering (Box 17)
        - Ertel, Intra (Box 17)
        - Jensen/Patterson; Natural Resources & Environment (Box 17)
        - Milne, M.; Romance Language (Box 17)
        - Ramuny, R.; Near East Studies (Box 17)
        - Simmons, Fajans; School of Public Health (Box 17)
        - Standifer, J.; Music (Box 17)
        - Tao, Hilda; Asian Languages (Box 17)
        - Wight, J.; Civil Engineering (Box 17)
        - General (Box 17)
      - 1990-Winter
        - Behar; LS&A (Box 17)
        - Bergstrom; LS&A (Box 17)
        - Dewar; Architecture (Box 17)
        - Gurin; LS&A (Box 17)
        - Janes; Library Studies (Box 17)
        - Neu; LS&A (Box 17)
        - Rasmussen; LS&A (Box 17)
        - Weiskopf; LS&A (Box 17)
        - General (Box 17)
        - Demond, A.; Engineering (Box 17)
        - Peterson, C.; Psychology (Box 17)
        - Vicinus, M.; LS&A (Box 17)
        - Webb, P.; Biology (Box 17)
        - Wolpoff, M.; Anthropology (Box 17)
        - Zweifler, A.; Internal Medicine (Box 17)
    - General 1976-1995
      - 1976-1992, 3 folders (Box 19)
      - 1994-95 (Box 19)
    - 1994/95
      - Winter 1995 Funded
        - Alcock, S., LS&A-Classical Studies (Box 19)
        - Arruda and Wineman, Engineering (Box 19)
        - Compton, K., Engineering (Box 19)
        - Eagle, H., LS&A-Residential College (Box 19)
        - Montgomery, S., Engineering (Box 19)
        - Morton, H., School of Natural Resources (SNRE) (Box 19)
        - Nori, F., LS&A-Physics (Box 19)
        - Reuter-Lorenz, P., LS&A-Psychology (Box 19)
        - Van der Pluijm, B., LS&A-Geology (Box 19)
    - 1995/96
      - General 1995/96 (Box 19)
      - Fall 1995 Funded
        - Bean, M., LS&A-Math (Box 19)
        - Gutierrez, L., LS&A-Psychology (Box 19)
        - Nooden, L., LS&A-Biology (Box 19)
        - Price, V., LS&A-Communication Studies (Box 19)
        - Robins, L., Medical School (Box 19)
      - Winter 1996 Funded
        - Haefner, H., Medical School (Box 19)
        - Kesler, S., LS&A-Geology (Box 19)
        - Kollman, K., LS&A-Political Science (Box 19)
        - Pedraza, S., LS&A-Sociology (Box 19)
        - Sastry, A., Engineering (Box 19)
        - Wang, C., Public Health (Box 19)
    - 1996/97
      - General 1996/97 (Box 20)
      - Winter 1997 Funded
        - Cascade, P., Medical School (Box 20)
        - Flint, A., Medical School (Box 20)
        - Gant, L., Social Work (Box 20)
        - Gutierrez and Ortega, Social Work (Box 20)
        - Kerner, N., LS&A-Chemistry (Box 20)
        - Lee, J., Nursing (Box 20)
        - Martin and Ammerlann, LS&A-Biology (Box 20)
        - O'Conner and Epstein, Education (Box 20)
        - Olsen, T., Engineering (Box 20)
        - Seifert, C., LS&A-Psychology (Box 20)
        - Turner, J., Architecture & Urban Planning (Box 20)
    - 1997/98
      - General, Winter 1998 (Box 20)
      - Winter 1998 Funded
        - Aparicio, F., LS&A-Romance Languages (Box 20)
        - Brown, T., School of Natural Resources (SNRE) (Box 20)
        - Burbank, J., LS&A-History (Box 20)
        - Chen, Q., LS&A-Asian Language and Culture (Box 20)
        - Grosh, K. Engineering (Box 20)
        - Hagerty, B., Nursing (Box 20)
        - Hogikyan, N., Medical School (Box 20)
        - Petty, W., Music (Box 20)
        - Smith, S., LS&A (Box 20)
    - 1998/99
      - General, Fall 1998 (Box 20)
      - Fall 1998 Funded
        - Arroyo and Benamou, LS&A-Romance Languages (Box 20)
        - Birge and Linetsky, Engineering (Box 20)
        - Brake, M., Engineering (Box 20)
        - Bright, C., LS&A-Residential College (Box 20)
        - Darling-Fisher, C., Nursing (Box 20)
        - Gross, M., Kinesiology (Box 20)
        - Jacobson and Leonard, Art & Design (Box 20)
        - Peters, T., Dentistry (Box 20)
        - Reeser, T., LS&A-Romance Languages (Box 20)
        - Spencer, M., Social Work (Box 20)
        - Thomas, D., LS&A-English (Box 20)
        - Weineck, S., LS&A-German (Box 20)
    - 1999-2000
      - General, Fall 1999 (Box 20)
      - Fall 1999 Unfunded
        - Boys, K., LS&A-Romance Languages (Box 20)
        - Kossoudji, S., LS&A-Economics (Box 20)
        - Lewis, R., LS&A-Physics (Box 20)
        - Ross, D., LS&A-Classical Studies (Box 20)
        - Sacerdoti, Y., LS&A-Near Eastern Studies (Box 20)
        - Seabury, B., Social Work (Box 20)
        - Shier, J., LS&A-Residential College (Box 20)
        - Shier and Myers, LS&A-Residential College (Box 20)
        - Tillinghast and Cogswell, LS&A (Box 20)
        - Williamson, J., Art & Design (Box 20)
      - Fall 1999 Funded
        - Aparicio, F., LS&A-Romance Languages (Box 20)
        - Baker, D., Medical School (Box 20)
        - Davies and Faller. Social Work (Box 20)
        - Dandekar, H., Architecture & Urban Planning (Box 20)
        - Gest, T., Medical School (Box 20)
        - Finn, J., Social Work (Box 20)
        - Gillespie, B., Engineering (Box 20)
        - Leonard, J., Art & Design (Box 20)
        - Olynyk, P., Art & Design (Box 20)
        - Peters, T., Dentistry (Box 20)
        - Pohl, J., Nursing (Box 20)
        - Porter, D., LS&A-English (Box 20)
  - Instructional Development Fund
    - 1973-1980
      - Aldridge, Sylvia and Martha Hyneck; Pharmacy 1978-1979 (Box 9)
      - Atkinson, John and Edward Walker; Psychology 1974-1975 (Box 9)
      - Andrews, Richard; Natural Resources 1977-1978 (Box 9)
      - Alexander, William; English 1973-1974 (Box 9)
      - Axelrod, Robert; Political Science 1977-1978 (Box 9)
      - Baker, Sheridan; English 1973-1974 (Box 9)
      - Barnes, Burton; Natural Resources 1974-1979, 2 folders (Box 9)
      - Beaver, Frank; Speech 1975-1976 (Box 9)
      - Becher, Brian; Natural Sciences 1979-1980 (Box 9)
      - Benson, Peter; Computer and Communication Science (Box 9)
      - Bentley, William; Natural Resources 1973-1974 (Box 9)
      - Berardi, Rosemary; Pharmacy 1975-1976 (Box 9)
      - Bernard, Sydney; Social Work 1978-1979 (Box 9)
      - Bertcher, Harvey; Social Work 1973-1975, 2 folders (Box 9)
      - Bertrand, Richard; Chemistry 1974-1975 (Box 9)
      - Bishop, Robert; Journalism 1973-1975 (Box 9)
      - Blumfiel, Charles; Mathematics 1973-1974 (Box 9)
      - Boros, Donald; Speech Communication and Theater 1974-1975 (Box 9)
      - Boyd, Eddie and Norman Lacina; Pharmacy 1976-1977 (Box 9)
      - Borer, Robert; Pediatrics 1975-1976 (Box 9)
      - Boys, Donald; Physics and Astronomy 1979-1980 (Box 9)
      - Brewin, Anne; Psychology 1974-1975 (Box 9)
      - Brilliant, Lawrence; Public Health 1977-1978 (Box 10)
      - Broomfield, John; History 1977-1978 (Box 10)
      - Brown, Terry; Landscape Architecture 1975-1976 (Box 10)
      - Brumfiel, Charles; Mathematics 1975-1976 (Box 10)
      - Burling, Robbins; Linguistics 1976-1977 (Box 10)
      - Burr, Harold; Engineering 1976-1977 (Box 10)
      - Cairns, J.R.; Engineering 1975-1976 (Box 10)
      - Carduner, Sylvie; Residential College 1976-1977 (Box 10)
      - Cares, Charles; Landscape Architecture 1974-1975 (Box 10)
      - Carroll, Raymond; Romance Languages 1978-1979 (Box 10)
      - Chesler, Mark; Sociology 1978-1979 (Box 10)
      - Clark, Walter; English 1973-1975, 2 folders (Box 10)
      - Clarkson, James; Geography 1977-1978 (Box 10)
      - Cleveland, D.E., Engineering 1978 (Box 10)
      - Clipson, Colin; Architecture and Urban Planning 1978-1979 (Box 10)
      - Colburn, C. William; Speech 1974-1975 (Box 10)
      - Coffin, Edna; Near Eastern Studies 1978-1979 (Box 10)
      - Dahlke, Richard; Mathematics 1975-1976 (Box 10)
      - Dancke, Gregory, Natural Resources 1979-1980 (Box 10)
      - Davis, Ken; English 1973-1974 (Box 10)
      - Debler, Walter; Applied Mechanics 1976-1977 (Box 10)
      - Deininger, Rolf; Environmental and Industrial Health 1973-1974 (Box 10)
      - Deprer, Charlene; Psychology 1976-1977 (Box 10)
      - Detwyler, Thomas; Geography 1974-1975 (Box 10)
      - Dew, James; Far Eastern Languages 1978-1979 (Box 10)
      - Dvorak, Tom; Music 1975-1978, 2 folders (Box 10)
      - Empedocles, Phillip; Chemistry 1973-1974 (Box 10)
      - English, Hubert; English 1974-1975 (Box 10)
      - Evans, B.J.; Geology 1973-1974 (Box 10)
      - Fabian, Hans; Germanic Language 1979-1980 (Box 10)
      - Fader, Lester; Architecture and Urban Planning (Box 10)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 10)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 10)
      - Faust, Halley; Epidemiology 1978-1979 (Box 10)
      - Feld, Sheila; School of Social Work 1973-1974 (Box 10)
      - Ferran, Peter; Residential College, Drama 1979-1980 (Box 10)
      - Filisko, Frank; Materials Engineering 1978-1979 (Box 10)
      - Folger, H.S.; Chemical Engineering 1974-1975 (Box 10)
      - Frye, William; Zoology 1973-1974 (Box 10)
      - Gies, Thomas; Business Administration 1973-1974 (Box 10)
      - Himes, Harold; Architecture 1973-1974 (Box 10)
      - Halpern, Jeanne; English 1977-1978 (Box 10)
      - Hamilton, Lee; Sociology 1978-1979 (Box 10)
      - Hannum, Micheal; Art and Photography 1978-1979 (Box 10)
      - Heirich, Max; Sociology 1978-1979 (Box 10)
      - Heirich, Jane; Residential College, Music 1978-1980 (Box 10)
      - Hendel, Fred; Physics 1974-1975 (Box 10)
      - Henry, Clement; Political Science 1975-1980 (Box 10)
      - Herrin, Gary; Industrial and Operations Engineering 1976-1977 (Box 10)
      - Hertzler, E.C.; Associate Dean University of Michigan Dearborn 1975-1976 (Box 10)
      - Hickey, Tom; Health and Gerontology 1979-1980 (Box 10)
      - Higgins, Tom; Psychology 1975-1976 (Box 10)
      - Hodge, Gerald; Medical and Biological Illustration 1979-1980 (Box 10)
      - Hornback, Bert; English 1978-1980 (Box 10)
      - Hosmer, LaRue; Business Administration 1976 (Box 10)
      - Ikuma, Hiroshi; Biology 1976-1977 (Box 10)
      - Ingram, William; English 1975-1976 (Box 10)
      - Jackson, Marion; Literature, Science and Arts Dean's Office 1977-1978 (Box 10)
      - Jacobsen, Harold; Political Science 1973-1974 (Box 10)
      - Jess, Paul; Journalism 1974-1975 (Box 10)
      - Jourdian, George; Biological Chemistry 1974-1975 (Box 10)
      - Kahn, Raymond; Anatomy 1973-1974 (Box 10)
      - Kinney, Mark; Project on Asian Studies in Education 1973-1974 (Box 10)
      - Kopplin, David, Eddie Floyd, and Lawrence Boyd; Psychology 1974-1975 (Box 10)
      - Kornbluh, Hy; Education 1979-1980 (Box 10)
      - Knudsvig, Glen; Classical Studies 1978-1979 (Box 10)
      - Koopman, James; Public Health 1978-1979 (Box 10)
      - Krause, Eugene; Mathematics (Box 10)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 10)
      - 1978-1980 (Box 10)
      - Kyes, Robert; German 1974-1975 (Box 10)
      - Larsen, Russell; Chemistry 1979-1980 (Box 10)
      - Leighton, Neil; University of Michigan-Flint 1977-1978 (Box 10)
      - Leonard, Joanne; Art 1979-1980 (Box 10)
      - Lourie, Margaret; Women's Studies 1973-1974 (Box 10)
      - Low, Bobbi; Resource Ecology 1974-1975 (Box 10)
      - MacAlpine, Gordon; Astronomy 1975-1976 (Box 10)
      - Mack, Dorothy; Humanities and English 1974-1975 (Box 10)
      - Malm, William; Ethnomusicolgy 1975-1976 (Box 10)
      - Marich, Milan; School of Education 1973-1974 (Box 10)
      - Marsh, David; Romance Languages 1978-1979 (Box 10)
      - Marsh, William; Physical Geography 1979-1980 (Box 10)
      - Marshall, Paul; Natural Resources 1978-1979 (Box 10)
      - May man, Martin; Psychology 1975-1976 (Box 11)
      - McCarus, Ernest; Near Eastern Studies 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Meeker, John; Literature, Science and Art-Dean's Office 1975-1976 (Box 11)
      - Meier, Peter; Public Health 1975-1976 (Box 11)
      - Mermier, Guy; Romance Languages 1979-1980 (Box 11)
      - Miller, Murray; Electrical Engineering 1975-1976 (Box 11)
      - Miller, Pat; Urban Planning 1976-1977 (Box 11)
      - Mills, Harriet; Far Eastern Language 1975-1976 (Box 11)
      - Morris, Barbara; English 1979-1980 (Box 11)
      - Morris, Janet; Mathematics 1978-1979 (Box 11)
      - Morton, Harrison; Natural Resources 1978-1979 (Box 11)
      - Munson, Richard; Pilot Program 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Nooden, Larry; Botany 1975-1976 (Box 11)
      - Nowack, Paul and Ron Widmar, Natural Resources 1978-1979 (Box 11)
      - Oakley, Bruce; Zoology 1974-1975 (Box 11)
      - Oakley, Deborah, Nursing 1978-1979 (Box 11)
      - Ogden, John; Far Eastern Language 1978-1979 (Box 11)
      - Oleinick, Arthur; Environmental Health 1979-1980 (Box 11)
      - Olson, Leslie; Humanities 1975-1976 (Box 11)
      - Olving, Gerhard; Architecture 1977-1978 (Box 11)
      - O'Neal, Elizabeth; English 1979-1980 (Box 11)
      - Palazzola, Guy; Art 1977-1978 (Box 11)
      - Papsdorf, James and Douglas Cornell 1974-1975 (Box 11)
      - Parmentier, Edward, Music 1978-1979 (Box 11)
      - Paris, Scott; Education and Psychology 1979-1980 (Box 11)
      - Rammuny, Raji, Near Eastern Studies 1979-1980 (Box 11)
      - Pastalan, Leon, Penelope Sahara and Susan Haberkorn, Gerontology 1974-1975 (Box 11)
      - Pepe, Steven; Law 1976-1977 (Box 11)
      - Polakowski, Kenneth; Natural Resources 1979-1980 (Box 11)
      - Pollak, Peter; Landscape Architecture 1974-1975 (Box 11)
      - Ramussen, Paul; Chemistry 1974-1975 (Box 11)
      - Reading and Learning Skills Center 1975-1976 (Box 11)
      - Reich, Victoria; Mental Health Research Institute 1978-1979 (Box 11)
      - Ribbons, William; Electrical Engineering 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Rosenberg, William; History 1977-1978 (Box 11)
      - Rosenthal, Marilyn; Behavioral Science 1978-1979 (Box 11)
      - Ross, Marc; Residential College 1976-1977 (Box 11)
      - Ruey, Hilda; Far Eastern Language and Literature 1974-1975 (Box 11)
      - Rush, Jon, Art 1973-1975, 2 folders (Box 11)
      - Sandman, Peter; Natural Resources 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Scott, R. C.; Mechanical Engineering 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Scheele, Robert; Landscape Architecture 1974-1975 (Box 11)
      - "Schooling in Corporate America" Conference 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Schroder, Mary; Nursing 1974-1975 (Box 11)
      - Schuman, Howard; Sociology 1978-1979 (Box 11)
      - Schwartz, Diane; Medical Center Library 1978-1979 (Box 11)
      - Simmons, Milagros; Environmental and Industrial Health 1979-1980 (Box 11)
      - Sokoloff, David; Physics 1976-1977 (Box 11)
      - Sonstegaard, David; Applied Mechanics and Engineering 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Sperl, George; Natural Science 1976-1977 (Box 11)
      - Spink, Walter; Art History 1979-1980 (Box 11)
      - Standifer, James; Music Education 1975-1980 (Box 11)
      - Steinwachs, Barbara; Extension Gaming Services 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Sweet, Waldo, and Glen Knudsvig; Classical Studies 1978-1979 (Box 11)
      - Thomas, Edwin; Social Work 1979-1980 (Box 11)
      - Todor, John; Physical Education 1979-1980 (Box 11)
      - Ulman, Betty; Biostatistics 1974-1975 (Box 11)
      - Vandermeer, John; Biology 1978-1979 (Box 11)
      - Vraciu, Robert; Hospital Administration 1978-1979 (Box 11)
      - Wang, Thomas; Landscape Architecture 1979-1980 (Box 11)